A Guide to the Records of T. Marshall Hahn Jr, 1962-1974
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series I, 1962-1965
  - Virginia Truck Experiment Station #1, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 288)
  - Virginia Truck Experiment Station #2, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 289)
  - Vice President and Dean of Graduate Studies: Dr. Warren W. Brandt #1, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 290)
  - Vice President and Dean of Graduate Studies: Dr. Warren W. Brandt #2, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 291)
  - Visiting Scholars Program, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 292)
  - Water Pollution Laboratory, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 293)
  - Mr. J.L.W. West, Jr., Executive Secretary to the President, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 294)
  - Y.M.C.A. Religious Activities: Mr. A.C. Payne, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 295)
  - A-Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 296)
  - Accountant: Mr. F.E. O' Connell, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 297)
  - Accrediting- National Commission on Accrediting- E.C.P.D., 1964 (Box 8, Folder 298)
  - Academic Council, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 299)
  - Admissions and Records: Dr. M.P. Lacy, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 300)
  - Aerospace Engineering: Dr. J.D. Eades, Department Head, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 301)
  - Agriculture: Dr. T.J. Horne, Director of Resident Instruction, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 302)
  - Agricultural Economics and Rural Sociology: Dr. H.M. Love, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 303)
  - College of Agriculture: Dr. Wilson B. Bell #1, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 304)
  - College of Agriculture: Dr. Wilson B. Bell #2, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 305)
  - Agronomy: Dr. H.L. Dunton, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 306)
  - Aircraft, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 307)
  - Alumni Association: Mr. M.L. Oliver, Secretary #1, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 308)
  - Alumni Association: Mr. M.L. Oliver, Secretary #2, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 309)
  - Alumni Association: Alphabetical #1, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 310)
  - Alumni Association: Alphabetical #2, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 311)
  - Alumni Association: Alphabetical #3, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 312)
  - Alumni President: Mr. C. Eugene Rowe, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 313)
  - American Society for Engineering Education, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 314)
  - Agricultural Engineering: Professor E.T. Swink, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 315)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 316)
  - American Council on Education, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 317)
  - Animal Science: Professor G.W. Litton, Department Head, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 318)
  - Appendices for Development of Center of Excellence in Systems Instrumentation, Analysis, and Control, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 318a)
  - Applications-Positions, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 319)
  - College of Architecture: Professor Charles Burchard, Dean, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 320)
  - College of Arts and Sciences: Dr. G.B. Johnston, Dean, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 321)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 322)
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 323)
  - Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges-National, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 324)
  - Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges- Southern, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 325)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 326)
  - B-Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 327)
  - Basketball, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 328)
  - Biology: Dr. F.S. Orcutt, Department Head, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 329)
  - Biochemistry and Nutrition: Dr. R.W. Engel, Department Head, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 330)
  - Boats, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 331)
  - Budget Director: Mr. L.M. Kuhn, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 332)
  - Budget Matters, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 333)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 334)
  - Business Manager: President's Fund, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 335)
  - Business Manager: Mr. S.K. Cassell, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 336)
  - College of Business: Dr. H.H. Mitchell, Department Head, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 337)
  - C-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 338)
  - Cement Plant: August-December #1, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 339)
  - Cement Plant: August-December #2, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 340)
  - Cement Plant: August-December #3, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 341)
  - Cement Plant: August-December #4, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 342)
  - CFDA- Meeting in New York, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 343)
  - Chemical Engineering: Dr. G.H. Beyer, Department Head, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 344)
  - Chemistry: Dr. R.C. King, Department Head, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 345)
  - Civil Rights, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 346)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 347)
  - Compact Among the States for the Improvement of Education, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 347a)
  - Corps, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 348)
  - Committee, Industrial, Facilities, Financing #1, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 349)
  - Committee, Industrial, Facilities, Financing #2, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 350)
  - Alexandria, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 351)
  - Harrisonburg, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 352)
  - Richmond, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 353)
  - Roanoke, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 354)
  - Wise, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 355)
  - Old Point Comfort, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 356)
  - Community Concert Association, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 357)
  - Continuing Education Center, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 358)
  - College Calendar, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 359)
  - Community Colleges: Dr. S.B. Row, Coordinator, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 360)
  - Consulting Work for Faculty, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 361)
  - D-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 362)
  - Dairy Science: Dr. J.R. Nichols, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 363)
  - Development Council, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 364)
  - Development #1, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 365)
  - Development #2, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 366)
  - Development #3, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 367)
  - Development #4, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 368)
  - Development #5, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 369)
  - Development #6, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 370)
  - Dining Hall: Mr. H. P. King, Director, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 371)
  - Donner Foundation, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 372)
  - Dormitory Director: Mr. J.E. Hardy, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 373)
  - E-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 374)
  - Easter Seal, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 375)
  - Edison Electric, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 376)
  - Employer Benefits, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 377)
  - Education: Dr. R.F. Beamer, Vocational and Business Education, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 378)
  - College of Engineering: Dr. W.G. Worchester, Dean, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 379)
  - Engineering Mechanics: Dr. D.F. Pletta, Department Head, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 380)
  - English and Foreign Language: Dr. M.L. Peacock, Department Head, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 381)
  - Entomology: Dr. J.M. Grayson, Department Head, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 382)
  - Enrollment Statistics, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 383)
  - Extension General, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 384)
  - Extension Director: Mr. W.H. Daughtrey, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 385)
  - F-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 386)
  - Faculty Committees, 1865 (Box 11, Folder 387)
  - Faculty List, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 388)
  - First National Exchange Bank, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 389)
  - Football, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 390)
  - Forestry and Wildlife: Dr. J.H. Hasner, Department Head, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 391)
  - G-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 392)
  - Geological Sciences: Dr. B.N. Cooper, Department Head, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 393)
  - Governor of Virginia, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 394)
  - Governor's Day- Alphabetical #1, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 395)
  - Governor's Day- Alphabetical #2, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 396)
  - Governor's Day- Alphabetical #3, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 397)
  - Governor's Day, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 398)
  - Graduate School: Dean F.W. Bull, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 399)
  - H-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 400)
  - Dr. T. Marshall Hahn, Jr., Personal, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 401)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 402)
  - Higher Education, Forms #1, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 403)
  - Higher Education, Forms #2, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 404)
  - Higher Education Study Commission, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 405)
  - Higher Education Study Commission #1, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 406)
  - Higher Education Study Commission #2, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 407)
  - Higher Education Study Commission #3, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 408)
- Series II, 1965-1967
  - Higher Education Study Commission #4, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 409)
  - Higher Education Study Commission #5, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 410)
  - Higher Education Study Commission #6, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 411)
  - History: Dr. Archer Jones, Department Head, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 412)
  - Homecoming Committee, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 413)
  - College of Home Economics: Dr. L.J. Harper, Dean, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 414)
  - Horticulture: Dr. W.P. Judkins, Department Head, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 415)
  - I-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 416)
  - Industrial Development- Richmond, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 417)
  - Industrial Engineering: Professor H.L. Manning, Department Head, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 418)
  - Invitations- Miscellaneous #1, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 419)
  - Invitations- Miscellaneous #2, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 420)
  - Invitations- Miscellaneous #3, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 421)
  - Infirmary: Dr. E.R. Irwin, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 422)
  - Invitations- Inauguration, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 423)
  - J-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 424)
  - J. Ambler Johnston, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 425)
  - K-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 426)
  - Chris Kraft, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 427)
  - L-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 428)
  - Legislation #1, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 429)
  - Legislation #2, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 430)
  - Legislation #3, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 431)
  - Library, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 432)
  - M-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 433)
  - Mathematics: Dr. Leon Rutland, Department Head, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 434)
  - McCormick Farm, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 435)
  - Mechanical Engineering: Dr. J. Beverly Jones, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 436)
  - Metals and Ceramics: Dr. J.F. Eckel, Department Head, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 437)
  - Military: Colonel E.D. Fitzpatrick; Colonel J.R. Finton, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 438)
  - Military Affairs Committee, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 439)
  - Minerals Resource Laboratory, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 440)
  - Mining Engineering: Professor J. Richard Lucas, Department Head, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 441)
  - Morrian Park - Westmoreland: Davis Memorial Foundation, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 442)
  - Mt. Ararat Foundation, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 443)
  - N-Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 444)
  - NASA, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 445)
  - NCAA, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 446)
  - National Science Foundation, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 447)
  - New Products, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 448)
  - O-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 449)
  - Outdoor Recreation, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 450)
  - P-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 451)
  - Personnel - Blacksburg: Mr. Evans, Director, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 452)
  - Personnel- Richmond: Mr. Garber, Director, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 453)
  - Philosophy and Religion: Dr. Norman Grover, Department Head, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 454)
  - Physical Education: Dr. W.E. McCubbin, Department Head, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 455)
  - Physics: Dr. J.A. Jacobs, Department Head, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 456)
  - Placement: Dr. W.H. Cato, Department Head, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 457)
  - Placement, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 458)
  - Publicity #1, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 459)
  - Publicity #2, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 460)
  - Publicity #3, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 461)
  - Planning Engineer: Mr. H.P.C. Vandenburg, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 462)
  - Poultry Science: Dr. C.E. Howes, Department Head, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 463)
  - Presidents Council #1, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 464)
  - Presidents Council #2, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 465)
  - Purchasing Agent: Mr. H.W. Swink, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 466)
  - Q-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 467)
  - R-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 468)
  - Registrar, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 469)
  - Research Park, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 470)
  - Reston, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 471)
  - Retirement- Presidents Council Committee, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 472)
  - Retirement, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 473)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 474)
  - S-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 475)
  - Salaries, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 476)
  - Scholarships: Harris F. Byrd, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 477)
  - Scholarships and Grants #1, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 478)
  - Scholarships and Grants #2, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 479)
  - Lon K. Savage, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 480)
  - Scholarships--Military, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 481)
  - Southern Conference, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 482)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 483)
  - Sheraton Hotel Guest Cards, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 484)
  - State Council of Education #1, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 485)
  - State Council of Education #2, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 486)
  - Statistics: Dr. Boyd Harshburger, Department Head, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 487)
  - State Department of Technical Education, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 488)
  - State Board of Education, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 489)
  - State Technical Services (General) #1, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 490)
  - State Technical Services (General) #2, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 491)
  - State Technical Services (General) #3, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 492)
  - State Technical Services (Alphabetical) #1, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 493)
  - State Technical Services (Alphabetical) #2, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 494)
  - Status for Women Commission #1, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 495)
  - Status for Women Commission #2, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 496)
  - Student Affairs: Dr. J.W. Dean, Dean of Students #1, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 497)
  - Student Affairs: Dr. J.W. Dean, Dean of Students #2, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 498)
  - Student Affairs: Dr. J.W. Dean, Dean of Students #3, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 499)
  - Student Affairs: J. Gordon Brown, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 500)
  - Student Affairs: Mr. A.C. Payne, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 501)
  - Student Letters: Parents and Friends- Others, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 502)
  - Student Letters: To and From, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 503)
  - Student Organizations, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 504)
  - Summer Conferences, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 505)
  - T-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 506)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 507)
  - Treasurer, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 508)
  - Technical Education, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 509)
  - Tech Festival, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 510)
  - U-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 511)
  - University Computing Center, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 512)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 513)
  - V-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 514)
  - V.A.R.C.: Dr. William H. McFarlane, Director #1, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 515)
  - V.A.R.C.: Dr. William H. McFarlane, Director #2, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 516)
  - V.A.R.C.: Dr. William H. McFarlane, Director #3, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 517)
  - Veterinary Science: Dr. D.F. Watson, Department Head, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 518)
  - Veterinary Science, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 519)
  - V.A.L.C., 1965 (Box 15, Folder 520)
  - Virginia Agriculture Conference Board, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 521)
  - Virginia Agriculture Experiment Station, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 522)
  - Virginia Department of Agriculture, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 523)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 524)
  - Virginia Tech Athletic Association: Mr. F.O. Mosley, Director, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 525)
  - Virginia Truck Experiment Station: Dr. H.W. Brittingham, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 526)
  - Vice President: Dr. Warren W. Brandt #1, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 527)
  - Vice President: Dr. Warren W. Brandt #2, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 528)
  - VPI Educational Foundation, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 529)
  - Visiting Scholar Program, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 530)
  - W-miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 531)
  - Water Pollution, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 532)
  - Water Resources, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 533)
  - YMCA: Mr. B.E. Trent, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 534)
  - A-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 535)
  - Academic Council #1, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 536)
  - Academic Council #2, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 537)
  - Academic Council #3, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 538)
  - Accrediting- National Committee on Accrediting, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 539)
  - Accountant: Mr. C.E. Burke, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 540)
  - Alcohol Beverage Control Board, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 541)
  - Admissions and Records: Dr. M.P. Lacy, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 542)
  - Aerospace Engineering: Dr. J.B. Eades, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 543)
  - College of Agriculture: Dean W.B. Bell, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 544)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 545)
  - Agronomy: Dr. H.L. Dutton, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 546)
  - Agricultural Engineering: Professor E.T. Swink, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 547)
  - Agriculture: Dr. T.J. Horne, Director of Residential Instruction, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 548)
  - Air University, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 549)
  - Aircraft, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 550)
  - Alumni- Alphabetical #1, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 551)
  - Alumni-Alphabetical #2, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 552)
  - Alumni Association #1, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 553)
  - Alumni Association #2, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 554)
  - Alumni Association #3, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 555)
  - Alumni Contributions- Alphabetical, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 556)
  - Alumni President: Mr. R.F. Willey, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 557)
  - Alumni- New York, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 558)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 559)
  - American Association of Engineering Education, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 560)
  - American Council on Education, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 561)
  - Animal Science: Professor D.W. Litton, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 562)
  - Applications- Positions, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 563)
  - College of Architecture: Dean Charles Burchard, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 564)
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities- Southern, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 565)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference #1, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 566)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference #2, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 567)
  - College of Arts and Sciences: Dean L.F. Malpass, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 568)
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities- National, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 569)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 570)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 571)
  - Attorney General, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 572)
  - B-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 573)
  - Basketball, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 574)
  - Bailey Research Trust, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 575)
  - Budget Director, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 576)
  - Biochemistry and Nutrition: Dr. R. W. Engel, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 577)
  - Dr. F.S. Orcult, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 578)
  - Blacksburg, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 579)
  - Boats, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 580)
  - Budget Matters, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 581)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 582)
  - College of Business: Dean H.H. Mitchell, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 583)
  - Business Manager: S.K. Cassell, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 584)
  - Business Manager President's Fund, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 585)
  - C-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 586)
  - Cement Plant, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 587)
  - Centennial, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 588)
  - Center for Economics Research and Business Services, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 589)
  - Center for Vocational and Technical Education, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 590)
  - Chemistry: Dr. Alan F. Clifford, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 591)
  - Chemical Engineering: Dr. G. H. Beyer, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 592)
  - Civil Rights, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 593)
  - College Calendar, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 594)
  - Colleges - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 595)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 596)
  - Community Colleges: Dr. S.B. Row, Director, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 597)
  - Commandant of Cadets: General M.W. Schewe, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 598)
  - University Computing Center, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 599)
  - Community Concert Association, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 600)
  - Conferences, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 601)
  - Consulting, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 602)
  - Counseling Center: Dr. Cannon and Dr. Cook, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 603)
  - Construction Engineering Research Laboratory, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 604)
  - Dairy Science: Dr. J.R. Nichols, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 605)
  - Deans- General, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 606)
  - Development #1, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 607)
  - Development #2, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 608)
  - Development Council, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 609)
  - Donner Foundation, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 610)
  - Dormitory Dedication, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 611)
  - Electrical Engineering, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 612)
  - Education: Dr. R.W. Beamer, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 613)
  - College of Engineering, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 614)
  - Engineering Mechanics: Professor D.H. Pletta, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 615)
  - English, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 616)
  - Enrollment Statistics, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 617)
  - Entomology: Dr. J.M. Grayson, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 618)
  - Extension- Director, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 619)
  - Extension- General, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 620)
  - F-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 621)
  - Faculty Committees, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 622)
  - Faculty Lists, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 623)
  - Ferrum Junior College, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 624)
  - First National Exchange Bank of Virginia, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 625)
  - Football, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 626)
  - Forestry and Wildlife: Dr. J.F. Hasner, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 627)
  - G-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 628)
  - Geological Sciences: Dr. B.N. Cooper, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 629)
  - Glee Club, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 630)
  - Governor of Virginia, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 631)
  - Governor's Day, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 632)
  - Governor's Day- Alphabetical, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 633)
  - Governor's Day- General, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 634)
  - Graduate School: Dr. F.W. Bull, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 635)
  - Graduate Committee, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 636)
  - H-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 637)
  - Dr. T. Marshall Hahn, Jr., Personal #1, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 638)
  - Dr. T. Marshall Hahn, Jr., Personal #2, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 639)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 640)
  - Higher Education Study Commission, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 641)
  - History: Dr. Archer Jones, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 642)
  - College of Home Economics: Dean Laura Jane Harper, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 643)
  - Honor Court, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 644)
  - Homecoming Committee, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 645)
  - Horticulture: Dr. W.P. Judkins, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 646)
  - Hospital, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 647)
  - I-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 648)
  - Industrial Engineering: Professor H.L. Manning, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 649)
  - Industrial Development- Richmond, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 650)
  - Industrial Facilities Financing for Virginia, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 650a)
  - Infirmary: Dr. E.R. Irwin, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 651)
  - J-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 652)
  - J. Ambler Johnston, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 653)
  - K-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 654)
  - L-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 655)
  - Legislation, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 656)
  - Legislation- Acts, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 657)
  - Legislation- General, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 658)
  - Library: Mr. F.C. Shirk, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 659)
  - Library Committee, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 660)
  - Lists, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 661)
  - M-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 662)
  - Mathematics: Dr. Leon. W. Rutland, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 663)
  - McCormick Farm Dedication, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 664)
  - McCormick Farm, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 665)
  - Mechanical Engineering: Dr. J.B. Jones, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 666)
  - Mr. Paul Mellon, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 667)
  - Metals and Ceramics: Dr. J.F. Eckel, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 668)
  - Military: Colonel E.D. Fitzpatrick; Colonel J.R. Finton, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 669)
  - Mining Engineering: Professor J. Richmond Lucas, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 670)
  - Moruan Park, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 671)
  - Miscellaneous- General #1, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 672)
  - Miscellaneous- General #2, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 673)
  - N-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 674)
  - Naming Buildings, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 675)
  - NASA, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 676)
  - NCAA, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 677)
  - National Science Foundation, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 678)
  - New Products, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 679)